http://www.cacert.org/policy/PrivacyPolicy.html

Name: PP COD5
Status: POLICY m20060629
Changes: 20060629
Editor:
Privacy Policy
0. Preliminaries
This policy discloses what information we gather about you when you visit any of our Web site, and when you issue or use our certificates. It describes how we use that information and how you can control it.
1. Website information
We collect two kinds of information about website users: 1) data that users volunteer by signing up to our website or when you send us an email via our contact form; and 2) aggregated tracking data we collect when users interact with our site.
2. Personal information
When you post to the contact form, you must provide your name and email address. When you sign up to the website, you must provide your name, email address, date of birth and some lost pass phrase question and answers.
We only share your information with any other organisation when so instructed by a CAcert arbitrator.
3. Aggregated tracking information
We analyse visitors' use of our sites by tracking information such as page views, traffic flow, search terms, and click through. We use this information to improve our sites. We also share this anonymous traffic and demographic information in aggregate form with advertisers and other business partners. We do not share any information with advertisers that can identify an individual user.
4. Cookies
Some of our advertisers use a third-party ad server to display ads. These ads may contain cookies. The ad server receives these cookies, and we don't have access to them.
We don't use cookies to store personal information, we do use sessions, and if cookies are enabled, the session will be stored in a cookie, and we do not look for cookies, apart from the session id. However if cookies are disabled then no information will be stored on or looked for on your computer.
5. Notification of changes
If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on www.CAcert.org. If we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users via email. Users will be able to opt out of any new use of their personal information.
6. How to update, correct, or delete your information
You are able to update, add and remove your information at any time via our web interface, log into the 'My Account' and then click on the 'My Details' section, and then click the relevant link
7. Privacy of certificates
CAcert does not automatically publish the certificates through a directory service or the website to other people than the user who requested the certificate. In the future, the user might be able to opt-in for publication of the certificates through a directory server by CAcert.
8. Privacy of user data
CAcert Assurers can see the name, birthday and the number of points by looking up the correct email address. No other person related data is published by CAcert.
9. Exceptions
A CAcert arbitrator may override this policy in a dispute.
To obtain access to confidential data, a dispute has to be filed.
10. Legal mandates
CAcert adopts the Australian privacy regulations.
Please see http://www.privacy.gov.au/ for further details.
Governmental warrants and civil supoenas will be processed through the dispute resolution system, which ensures that valid authority is given to whoever complies with the supoena or the warrant.
If you need to contact us in writing, address your mail to:
CAcert Inc.
PO Box 66
Oatley NSW 2223
Australia
